Guide to the Elsie H. Hillman Papers, 1920-2015 AIS.2013.02
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Audio-Video Material, 1974-2012; XIV.
  - UPMC Hillman Cancer Center, Opening News Coverage, 2002; VHS Cassette (Shelf WW 1-E-1, Item 35)
  - WQED Elsie Awards, 2002; VHS Cassette (Shelf WW 1-E-1, Item 36)
  - WQED Elsie Awards,"On Q" Interviews Fred Rogers, 2002; VHS Cassette (Shelf WW 1-E-1, Item 37)
  - WQED FM, Remembering Fred Rogers, 2003; Audio CD (Shelf WW 1-E-1, Item 38)
  - Calvary Episcopal Church, Adult Forum Post Convention Report, 2004; Audio Cassette (Shelf WW 1-E-1, Item 39)
  - "Nixon Conversations 1971", 2004; Audio CD (Shelf WW 1-E-1, Item 40)
  - UPMC Hillman Cancer Center, Donation Announcement and Press Conference, June 20, 2005; MiniDV (Shelf WW 1-E-1, Item 41)
  - Shady Side Academy, Hillman Center For the Performing Arts Dedication Celebration, 2004; Audio CD (Shelf WW 1-E-1, Item 42)
  - UPMC Gala Video Production, 2004; VHS Cassette (Shelf WW 1-E-1, Item 43)
  - WQED Elsie Awards, 2004; VHS Cassette (Shelf WW 1-E-1, Item 44)
  - WQED Elsie Awards, "On Q" from the Elsie Awards, 2004 (Shelf WW 1-E-1, Item 45)
  - Pennsylvania Cable Network, Dick Thornburgh: An Oral History, 2005; DVD (Shelf WW 1-E-1, Item 46)
  - Pennsylvania Cable Network, Scranton for Governor Campaign Fundraiser, 2005; DVD (Shelf WW 1-E-1, Item 47)
  - Mentoring Partnership Awards Dinner, Bishop Donald Wuerl's message of congratulations, 2006; Betacam (Shelf WW 1-E-1, Item 48)
  - Run Baby Run, 2006; MiniDV (Shelf WW 1-E-1, Item 49)
  - Pittsburgh Magazine, Disc of Images used in story on Elsie and Henry Hillman, 2007; CD-ROM (Shelf WW 1-E-1, Item 50)
  - International Women's Forum World Leadership Conference International Hall of Fame Gala, 2008; DVD (Shelf WW 1-E-1, Item 51)
  - Pittsburgh Promise, Leaders TV Ad, c. 2008-2009; DVD (Shelf WW 1-E-1, Item 52)
  - Nate Smith Documentary, What does Trouble Mean? Nate Smith's Revolution, 2009; DVD (Shelf WW 1-E-1, Item 53)
  - StoryCorps Interview with grandson Henry Simonds, 2010; Audio CD (Shelf WW 1-E-1, Item 54)
  - Forbes Funds, Elsie Hillman awarded Frieda Shapira Medal, 2011; DVD (Shelf WW 1-E-1, Item 55)
  - Never a Spectator: The Political Life of Elsie Hillman, Video Production for Carnegie Museum Event, 2012; DVD (Shelf WW 1-E-1, Item 56)
  - Governor Tom Ridge - Message for Elsie Hillman, VHS Cassette (Shelf WW 1-E-1, Item 57)
  - The Pittsburgh Downtown Plan CD-Rom, CD-ROM (Shelf WW 1-E-1, Item 58)
  - UPMC Hillman Cancer Center, Major Donor Preview, VHS Cassette (Shelf WW 1-E-1, Item 59)
  - Elsie Hillman speaking about County Commissioner Race, VHS Cassette (Shelf WW 1-E-1, Item 60)